swrve.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy | Swrve - Mobile Marketing Automation : Analytics, A/B Testing, In-App Campaigns, Push Notifications

## Privacy

Swrve has drafted this Privacy Policy to explain (i) how we use data you provide to us through this Website and (ii) how we use the data we collect when users use applications or play games which make use of the Swrve Service.

Privacy is important to us. We have established this Privacy Policy to explain how information is collected, protected, used and disclosed by us and through our Website and the Swrve Service.

Our Privacy Policy will be updated from time to time. Should our privacy practices change, we will post the policy changes on the Website and indicate the date the Privacy Policy was last updated. We encourage you to check back at our Website periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.

This Privacy Policy is divided into two sections, the first deals with information that we collect via this Website and the second deals with information that we collect via our customers’ applications or games which utilize the Swrve Service. In the second case, our customers are providing user information to us, but we also wanted to outline to users how we, in turn, use and share that information.

### Website

#### Manually-Inputted Information

You can visit and browse the Swrve Website without providing any information about yourself. You may voluntarily provide personal information, such as contact information, or we may ask for such information in various forms on this Website, including requests for product or service information, white papers, registration for Webinars etc.

We may use your email address or other contact information you give us to contact you with product or service information. If we ask for your preferences (e.g. in relation to games, platforms etc), we will only use that information to tailor our communications to you. We may also use preference information on an aggregated basis (where you are not personally identifiable) for our business, research, product development and marketing purposes. Other than as outlined below, we do not make personally identifiable information available to any third party and we do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties.

#### Automatically-Collected Information

When you access the Swrve Website, some information may be automatically collected, such as your computer's or mobile device’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's or mobile device’s operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and the time and date of your visit.

The Website use cookies. A "cookie" is a small text file placed on your computer's or mobile device’s hard drive by a web server - which is acknowledged by your web browser which acts to identify your computer. Cookies are used to collect and send information about your website visit – for example, number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, navigation history through the website and other statistics. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Website and the Swrve Services. Cookies cannot be used to access any other data on your computer and cannot be used to personally identify you. You can prevent cookies being placed on your hard drive by setting your internet browser settings to not accept cookies.

Where you do provide personal or contact information, you may not provide false information about yourself.

#### Swrve Service - Users

When you download, pay for or play a game or use an application which uses the Swrve Service (i.e. an app/game developed by a Swrve customer), the privacy policy that applies is the one between you and the game or application developer or provider (“Developer”). In order to offer the Swrve Service to Developers, we require that they obtain permission from you to share certain information with us. This information may be “personal” information, such as your name, address, contact details and social network user information (“Personal Data”). Information collected may also be non-personal information, such as mobile device information like operating system and hardware type, IP address, UDID/MAC address, your gameplay habits and preferences, game platforms and media, geographic location, gender and age (“User Data”).

We do not require access to sensitive personal information, such as medical or health information; racial or ethnic origin; political opinions; religious or philosophical beliefs; sexual orientation.

#### How We Use your Information

We use User Data make the Swrve Service and its features available to our Developers, which includes allowing Developers to customise your online experience to your preferences and allowing Developers to target content to users based on in-game and in-app behavior.

We may use User Data to enhance the Swrve Service. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

We use User Data in aggregate or anonymized form (such that users are not personally identifiable) for our business, research, product development and marketing purposes.

#### How We Share your Information

We may share our data, including personal information about you, with our subsidiary companies. Disclosure of your information to third parties. In addition to the other purposes outlined in this policy, we may share:

  * any information or data in response to a verified request by law enforcement, immigration, customs or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity.
  * User Data with our business partners or for product development, marketing or public relations – information shared is limited to aggregated or anonymized data.
  * any information or data with our hosting provider who may only use the information to administer our Website and the Swrve Services. The hosting provider is required to keep all information private and secure
  * Any information in connection with any merger, sale of Swrve’s assets, or a financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another entity.

#### How to Edit Your Information

You may ask us to delete any personal information you have provided directly to us at any time. We do retain the right to use the aggregate data we have collected, provided that such data does not personally identify you.

You may also contact your game/application provider to edit or delete information held about you. When we receive a request from a Developer to amend or delete Personal Information, we shall promptly do so.

#### Access To Persons under 13 years

The Website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. The Website and Swrve Services are not developed or directed at children, although some of the games and applications using the Swrve Services may be directed at children under 13. We do not knowingly solicit or collect any personally identifiable from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly market the Website and Swrve Services to children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 contrary to local laws, we will delete that information as soon as possible. Please contact us atprivacy@swrve.com if you have reason to believe that any personal information from or about a child under 13 has been provided to us without the appropriate consent.

#### End User Opt-Out - Facebook Campaign Tracking

Some of our customers who advertise on Facebook ask us to track data related to how many and which people who have seen an advertisement then install a game/app. In this case, Swrve tracks this information anonymously and cannot link that information to a named Facebook user. However, users may, in any case, ask us to cease tracking such information. To do so, please provide us with the your MAC Address and we will cease to track such information. Please allow up to 10 days for the request to be implemented on our systems.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or our information practices you can contact us by emailing us at privacy@swrve.com  
This document was last updated on April 8th, 2013

Swrve New Media Inc.,  
575 Market Street, #2725 San Francisco, CA 94105, USA  
New Game Technologies Limited t/a Swrve  
9 Windsor Place,  
Pembroke Street Lower  
Dublin 2, Ireland  
Company Reg #449422
